Finding Aid for Junius E. Beal Papers
Bentley Historical Library
Junius E. Beal Papers
1869-1946
Bentley Historical Library
Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942
85884 Aa 2
15.3 linear feet
Ann Arbor, Michigan, businessman, publisher of Ann Arbor Courier, Republican politician, and regent of University of Michigan. Correspondence, letter books, speeches, newspaper clippings, and photographs; papers (1909-1920) of Michigan Public Domain Commission, of which Beal was a member; papers (1877-1904) concerning Port Huron Gas Light Company; and printed material and miscellanea (1885-1905) concerning League of American Wheelmen and his interest in bicycling.
A portion of the collection was donated by Mrs. Junius Beal (donor no. 1176 ) in 1942. The great bulk of Beal's papers were donated by his daughter Mrs. Albert Jacobs (donor no. 3046 ) and came to the library in the period of 1967-1970.
The collection is open for research.
Junius E. Beal was born February 23, 1860 in Port Huron, Michigan. He graduated from the University of Michigan in 1882, then assumed the editorship of the Ann Arbor Weekly Courier and the Daily Times which he had inherited from his foster father Rice A. Beal. He remained as editor until 1904. Beal was also instrumental in the development of the Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti interurban in 1889, and was president of the firm until 1896. He also served as manager of the Ann Arbor Electric Light Co., 1894-1902. He was also president of the Port Huron Gas Co. during that same period.
Beal, in addition to business interests, was also civically involved. He served on the Ann Arbor Board of Education from 1884 to 1904; he filled one term (1905-1906) as state legislator in the Michigan House of Representatives; and from 1908 to 1919, he served on the Michigan Public Domain Commission where he helped further a state reforestation program.
Beal was most noteworthy in his work as regent of the University of Michigan. He served four 8-year terms from 1907 to 1939. Among his accomplishments on the board were his advocacy of a building program that saw the construction of the football stadium and Hill Auditorium. Beal was also involved in the selection of U-M presidents.
Beal died June 24, 1942.
The Junius E. Beal papers include correspondence, papers accumulated from his various interests and organizational activities, subject files, speeches, newspaper clippings, and photographs. The series in the collection include: Correspondence, Michigan Public Domain Commission, Topical Files; and Other Materials. Most of the files in the collection relate in some way to Beal's life in Ann Arbor, either as a student, a businessman, a public figure, as someone who took civic responsibility seriously and was determined to serve his community and the university that he loved.
African Americans.; Ann Arbor (Mich.); Belgium.; Conservation of natural resources -- Michigan.; Cycling.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1894.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1896.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1904.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1908.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1910.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1912.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1914.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1916.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1918.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1920.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1922.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1924.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1926.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1928.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1930.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1932.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1934.; Elections -- Michigan -- 1936.; Hawaii.; Michigan -- Politics and government -- 1837-1950.; Michigan -- Politics and government -- 1877-1898.; Michigan -- Politics and government -- 1899-1916.; Michigan -- Politics and government -- 1917-1921.; Michigan -- Politics and government -- 1922-1928.; Michigan -- Politics and government -- 1929-1938.; Philippines -- History -- 1898-1946.; Street-railroads -- Michigan.; Temperance -- Michigan.; World War, 1914-1918.; Ann Arbor (Mich.) -- Dwellings.; Ann Arbor (Mich.) -- Streets.; Bicycles and tricycles.; Cemeteries -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Cycling -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Dwellings -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Forestry.; Lumber industry.; Streets -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Photographs.; Ann Arbor courier.; Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.; Beal, Rice Aner, 1823-1883.; Beta Theta Pi. Lambda Chapter (University of Michigan); Detroit Bicycle Club.; First Methodist Church (Ann Arbor, Mich.); League of American Wheelmen.; Methodist Episcopal Church -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Republican Party (Mich.); Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930.; University of Michigan. Board of Regents.; University of Michigan. Class of 1882.; University of Michigan. President.; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924.; Ann Arbor Bicycle Club.; Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.; Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925.; Chelsea Methodist Home.; Forest Hill Cemetery (Ann Arbor, Mich.); League of American Wheelmen. Michigan Division.; Michigan. Legislature.; Michigan. Public Domain Commission.; University of Michigan. Board of Regents.; University of Michigan. Chinese Students Club.; University of Michigan. School of Natural Resources.; University of Michigan -- Students -- Social life and customs -- 1901-1910.; Abbot, Willis J. (Willis John), 1863-1934.; Adams, Henry Carter, 1851-1921.; Alger, R. A. (Russell Alexander), 1836-1907.; Alger, Frederick Moulton, 1876-1933.; American Bible Society.; Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.; Ann Arbor Street Railway Company.; Baird, Charles, 1870-1944.; Bates, Henry Moore, 1869-1949.; Beakes, Samuel Willard, 1861-1927.; Brown, Prentiss M. (Prentiss Marsh), 1889-1973.; Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.; Burrows, Julius C. (Julius Caesar), 1837-1915.; Burton, Marion Le Roy, 1874-1925.; Chase, A. W. (Alvin Wood), 1817-1885.; Clements, William L. (William Lawrence), 1861-1934.; Comstock, William Alfred, 1877-1949.; Cooley, Mortimer E. (Mortimer Elwyn), 1855-1944.; Copeland, Royal S. (Royal Samuel), 1868-1938.; Couzens, James, 1872-1936.; Cramton, Louis C. (Louis Convers), 1875-; Daniels, Josephus, 1862-1948.; Dickinson, Luren Dudley, 1859-1943.; Diekema, Gerrit John, 1859-1930.; Fairlie, John A. (John Archibald), 1872-1947.; Fellows, Grant, 1865-1929.; Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1853-1928.; Florer, Warren Washburn, 1869-1958.; Fordney, Joseph W. (Joseph Warren), 1853-1932.; Fuller, Oramel B., 1858-; Gore, Victor M.; Grant, John Henry, 1857-1913.; Green, Fred W. (Fred Warren), 1872-1936.; Groesbeck, Alexander J. (Alexander Joseph), 1873-1953.; Guest, Edgar A. (Edgar Albert), 1881-1959.; Hanchett, Benjamin Sawtell, 1868-1933.; Hayden, Joseph Ralston, 1887-1945.; Hinsdale, W. B. (Wilbert B.), 1851-1944.; Hobbs, William Herbert, 1864-1952.; Holt, Hamilton, 1872-1951.; Hubbard, Lucius L. (Lucius Lee), 1849-1933.; Hudson, Grant Martin, 1868-1955.; Hudson, Joseph Lowthian, 1846-1912.; Hutchins, Harry B. (Harry Burns), 1847-1930.; Hutchins, Robert Maynard, 1899-1977.; Johnson, Elias Finley, 1861-1933.; Kahn, Albert, 1869-1942.; Kelley, Patrick Henry, 1867-1925.; Kelsey, Francis W. (Francis Willey), 1858-; King, Paul H.; Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930.; Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.; Koch, Theodore Wesley, 1871-1941.; Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1890-1961.; League to Enforce Peace.; Leland, Frank Bruce.; Lindsey, Ben B. (Ben Barr), 1869-1943.; Little, Clarence C. (Clarence Cook), 1888-; Loud, George Alvin, 1852-1925.; Lowden, Frank O. (Frank Orren), 1861-1943.; McKinley, William, 1843-1901.; McMillan, James, 1838-1902.; Malcolm, George A. (George Arthur), 1881-1961.; Michener, Earl C. (Earl Cory), 1876-1957.; Michigan. Public Domain Commission.; Michigan Audubon Society.; Michigan Pioneer and Historical Society.; Mott, Charles Stewart, 1875-1973.; Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.; National Economic League (U.S.); National Home Finding Society for Colored Children.; Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), 1860-; Osmeña, Sergio, 1878-1961.; Patton, John, 1850-1907.; Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946.; Poindexter, Miles, 1868-1946.; Port Huron Gas Light Company.; Powers, Perry Francis, 1857-1945.; Ramos, Alfredo.; Rich, John Treadway, 1841-1926.; Root, Elihu, 1845-1937.; Roth, Filibert, 1858-1925.; Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-1971.; Sawyer, Walter H. (Walter Hulme), 1861-1931.; Sink, Charles A. (Charles Albert), 1879-1972.; Sleeper, Albert E., 1862-1934.; Smith, Henry Cassorte, 1859-1911.; Smith, John McMunn C., 1853-1923.; Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.; Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.; Spaulding, Thomas M. (Thomas Marshall), 1882-; Stone, Ralph, 1868-1956.; Townsend, Charles E. (Charles Elroy), 1856-1924.; Tyler, Moses Coit, 1835-1900.; United States. Fuel Administration.; Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.; Vaughan, Coleman C., 1857-; Vaughan, Victor C. (Victor Clarence), 1851-1929.; Warner, Frederick Maltby, 1865-1923.; Washington, Booker T., 1856-1915.; Watkins, Lucius Whitney, 1873-; Wedemeyer, William Walter, 1873-1913.; Wenley, R. M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929.; White, William Allen, 1868-1944.; Wood, Leonard, 1860-1927.; Worcester, Dean C. (Dean Conant), 1866-1924.; Yost, Fielding Harris, 1871-1946.
- Correspondence, 1880-1946; 10.3 linear feet
  Correspondence is the largest series (10.3 linear ft.; 1880-1946) in the collection. Documented is not only the wide variety of individuals with whom Beal corresponded, but also his many organizational and public activities, notably those relating to the University of Michigan.
  - Undated, 1880-June 1908; 29 folders (Box 1)
  - July 1908-July 1910, 24 folders (Box 2)
  - August 1910-December 1912, 25 folders (Box 3)
  - 1913-January 1916, 25 folders (Box 4)
  - February 1916-March 1918, 27 folders (Box 5)
  - April 1918-December 1924, 34 folders (Box 6)
  - 1925-1927, 27 folders (Box 7)
  - 1928-June 1930, 31 folders (Box 8)
  - July 1930-May 1933, 36 folders (Box 9)
  - June 1933-June 1937, 40 folders (Box 10)
  - July 1937-1946, 9 folders (Box 11)
- Michigan Public Domain Commission
  - Undated, 1909-1920; 11 folders, 1 volume (Box 11)
- Topical Files
  The other noteworthy series is the Topical Files where have been placed files relating to Beal's interests in business, politics, bicycling, and regental concerns. Here will be found photographs in the collection. These consists of informal photos; photos of Beal with various groups; photos of Ann Arbor houses and other views; lumbering and forestry photographs (probably California); and a photo of William Jennings Bryan's visit to Ann Arbor (1896?).
  - Ann Arbor file, 1870s-1940; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Ann Arbor Printing Company file, 1875-1902 (Box 12)
  - Appointment calendars, 1912-1918 (Box 12)
    (sample)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1891-1939; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Bicycling
    - Printed material concerning the League of American Wheelmen and bicycle tours, 1885-1905; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Bound document presented to American cyclists by Birchfield Wheeling Club, Birmingham, Eng, 1889 (Box 16)
  - Masons, 1879-1938 (Box 12)
  - Member cards and certificates, 1887-1927 (Box 12)
  - Methodist Church, 1883-1929 (Box 12)
  - Miscellanea, 4 folders (Box 12)
  - Photographs, 4 envelopes (Box 13)
    (see also oversize photographs in box 16)
    - Portraits of Beal and group photos (Box 13)
      (Includes photo of Beal with William Jennings Bryan in Ann Arbor)
    - Lumbering and Forestry, 10 items (Box 13)
    - Ann Arbor House and Street View, 3 items (Box 13)
      (see also box 16 outsize)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - League of American Wheelmen and other groups (Box 16)
      (outsize photos, includes 1913 U of M Chinese Student Club, 1905 legislature reunion and unidentified groups)
  - Port Huron Gas Light Company, 1877-1904; 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Republican politics, 1881-1937; 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Society of Colonial Wars/Sons of the American Revolution, 1914-1938 (Box 13)
  - Speeches, 1923-1939; undated; 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Student papers of Junius Beal, 1882; undated (Box 13)
  - University of Michigan, undated; 1877-1909; 3 folders (Box 13)
  - University of Michigan, 1910-1939; 3 folders (Box 14)
- Other Materials
  - Newspaper clippings, 1869-1939; 10 folders (Box 14)
  - Pocket notebooks, 1885-1906 (Box 14)
  - Letterpress books, 1886-1895 (Box 15)
  - Account books, 1883-1906 (Box 15)
  - Citations, appointments, etc (Box 16)
  - Oversized items
    (contents listed above)
Selective Index of Correspondents
Abbot, Willis John, 1863-1934.
July 19, 1933
Adams, Henry Carter, 1851-1921.
Mar. 4, 1910; June 4, 1920
Alger, Russell Alexander, 1836-1907.
Feb. 9; 1897
Alger, Frederick Moulton, 1876-1933.
Oct. 14, 1910; Oct. 28, 1910
American Bible Society
Correspondence throughout
Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.
Undated; Dec. 1; 1892; July 3; 1897; Oct. 10, 1904; Mar. 23, 1907; Apr. 23, 1907, 1908-1909; Oct. 27, 1910
Ann Arbor Street Railway Company
1896
Anti-Saloon League/Prohibition letters
Dec. 26, 1907; July 9, 1908; Sept. 16, 1909; Dec. 20, 1909; Feb. 6, 1910; Mar. 12, 1910; Mar. 18, 1910; Apr. 14, 1910; May 20, 1910; Feb. 3, 1911; Mar. 15, 1911; May 18, 1911; Sept. 26, 1911; Jan. 4, 1912; June 4, 1912; Nov. 3, 1914; Jan. 26, 1915; Apr. 1, 1915; [1916?]; [1916?]; [1917?]; Mar. 29, 1917; Aug. 23, 1917; [1922?]; Aug. 3, 1922; Nov. 27, 1922; Nov. 29, 1922; Apr. 13, 1925; Apr. 22, 1925; Apr. 25, 1925; June 26, 1925; [1926?]; Apr. 15, 1926; June 22, 1926; Jan. 20, 1927; Feb. 2, 1927; Feb. 3, 1927; Apr. 26, 1927; July 22, 1927; Aug. 10, 1927; July 27, 1928; Aug. 20, 1928; Aug. 29, 1928; Oct. 24, 1928; Jan. 22, 1929; [1930?]; Feb. 8, 1930; Feb. 19., 1930; Mar. 8, 1930; Mar. 13, 1930; May 3, 1930; May 26, 1930; July 25, 1930; Sept. 2, 1930; Oct. 30, 1930; July 9, 1931; Feb. 1, 1932; Feb., 1932; undated; Feb. 24, 1932; Mar. 9, 1932; Mar. 14, 1932; Mar. 22, 1932; May 17, 1932; May 25, 1932; June 10, 1932; Aug. 19, 1932; Sept. 6, 1932; Sept. 12, 1932; Sept. 15, 1932; Sept. 27, 1932; Sept. 20, 1932; [1932?]; July 5, 1933; Oct. 31, 1934; June 12, 1935; Aug. 3, 1938
Baird, Charles, 1870-1944.
Feb. 13, 1908; Apr. 25, 1914; Feb. 18, 1921; Dec. 28, 1926; Sept. 11, 1929; Sept. 16, 1929; Sept. 11, 1935; Oct. 21, 1936; Dec. 24, 1938; Jan. 10, 1939; Dec. 23, 1939
Bates, Henry Moore, 1869-1949.
Undated; Oct. 10, 1904; June 17; 1908; May 29, 1909, 1912; Oct. 30, 1913; Oct. 13, 1914, 1917; Feb. 12, 1918; Dec. 22, 1919; May 6, 1920; May 13, 1920; Feb. 8, 1921, 1924; Jan. 5, 1925; Jan. 9, 1925; Feb. 1, 1929, 1930; June 6, 1931; July 2, 1931; Mar. 29, 1934; Nov. 1934; Dec. 4, 1936; Nov. 1, 1938
Beakes, Samuel Willard, 1861-1927
Apr. 21; 1886; Apr. 24; 1886; Aug. 16, 1901; Mar. 30, 1911; Oct. 13, 1914, 1916; Feb. 1, 1917, 1918
Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889
Apr. 27, 1937; Apr. 28, 1937
Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.
Apr. 28, 1930, 1931-1933, 1936
Burrows, Julius Caesar, 1837-1915
Nov. 24, 1904; June 16, 1905; Jan. 22, 1909
Burton, Marion LeRoy, 1874-1925.
Dec. 4, 1919; Dec. 31, 1919, 1920-1924
Chase, Alvin Wood, 1817-1885.
Nov. 29; 1898
Clements, William Lawrence, 1861-1934.
Oct. 6, 1909; Oct. 26, 1909, 1910-1912; Dec. 12, 1913, 1914-1918, 1920-1930; Feb. 11, 1931; Apr. 15, 1931, 1932-1933
Comstock, William Alfred, 1877-1949.
June 17, 1913; Oct. 1, 1925; Oct. 12, 1925; Dec. 23, 1927; July 6, 1934
Cooley, Mortimer Elwyn, 1855-1944.
Correspondence throughout
Copeland Royal Samuel, 1868-1938.
Nov. 18, 1901; Mar. 3, 1910; Mar. 24, 1910; Sept. 24, 1910; June 5, 1912; Feb. 8, 1926; Mar. 25, 1936
Couzens, James Joseph, 1872-1936.
Apr. 22, 1932; Feb. 28, 1935
Cramton, Louis Convers, 1875-1966.
Aug. 31, 1916
Daniels, Josephus, 1862-1948.
Sept. 5, 1917
Dickinson, Luren Dudley, 1859-1943.
Feb. 5, 1907; Nov. 15, 1909; Mar. 10, 1910; June 11, 1910, 1914; Mar. 8, 1917, 1924; undated, 1926; Mar. 30, 1928; Apr. 16, 1928; Jan. 28, 1931; Oct. 31, 1934; Mar. 21, 1936; Mar. 25, 1936
Diekema, Gerrit John, 1859-1930.
Sept. 14, 1908; Apr. 6, 1912
Fairlie, John Archibald, 1872-1947.
May 7; 1908; June 10, 1908
Fellows, Grant, 1865-1929.
Nov. 11, 1904; Sept. 20, 1910; Sept. 30, 1910; Jan. 25, 1915; Nov. 2, 1915, 1916; Feb. 7, 1923; Feb. 19, 1923
Ferris, Woodbridge Nathan, 1853-1928.
May 20, 1913; Aug. 4, 1913; Oct. 18, 1913; Jan. 23, 1914; July 28, 1914, 1915; Jan. 15, 1916; Apr. 5, 1917; July 2, 1917; Dec. 20, 1918; July 6, 1923
Florer, Warren Washburn, 1869-1958.
1916; Jan. 14, 1917; Feb. 11, 1917; May 27, 1917; Nov. 30, 1928
Fordney, Joseph Warren, 1853-1932.
Feb. 11, 1916; Feb. 17, 1916; Oct. 20, 1927
Fuller, Oramel B, 1858-
July 30, 1908; Sept. 14, 1908; Dec. 22, 1909; Sept. 26, 1910; Nov. 17, 1910; Jan. 6, 1911; Sept. 13, 1912; Sept. 12, 1913; Nov. 22, 1913, 1914-1918, 1920; Mar. 17, 1921; June 15, 1921; July 7, 1922; Feb. 20, 1924; Aug. 14, 1924; Aug. 1, 1925; Mar. 18, 1931
Gore, Victor Michael, 1858-1941.
Feb. 13, 1913; Apr. 11, 1913, 1914-1920, 1922; Nov. 8, 1923, 1924-1925; Aug. 14, 1926; Aug. 30, 1927, 1928-1930; Nov. 2, 1931, 1932, 1935; Aug. 15, 1938; Jan. 5, 1939; Sept. 28, 1939
Grant, John Henry, 1857-1913
Oct. 18; 1883; Apr. 10; 1886; Apr. 30; 1886; 1894; 1896, 1901; Aug. 9, 1902; Dec. 23, 1902; Jan. 19, 1903, 1907, 1909-1912
Green, Fred Warren, 1872-1936.
Mar. 20, 1915; Sept. 13, 1920; Apr. 5, 1923; Aug. 25, 1924; Feb. 19, 1927; Oct. 2, 1928, 1929; May 26, 1930; Oct. 31, 1932
Groesbeck, Alexander J., 1873-1953.
Nov. 29, 1920
Guest, Edgar Albert, 1881-1959.
Feb. 25, 1929; Feb. 27, 1929; Mar. 19, 1934
Hanchett, Benjamin Sawtell, 1868-1933.
1911; June 22, 1912, 1914-1916; Oct. 10, 1917; Dec. 5, 1919, 1922, 1924; June 15, 1926; Dec. 26, 1928; Sept. 24, 1929, 1931
Hawaiian Islands
Letters with Lucius Van Slyke; 1885-1886
Hayden, Joseph Ralston, 1887-1945.
June 22, 1917; June 30, 1917; July 11, 1917; May 15, 1934; Apr. 2, 1937
Hinsdale, Wilbert Bartlett, 1851-1941.
June 4, 1909; Oct. 26, 1910, 1911; Mar. 5, 1912; Apr. 9, 1912; Mar. 25, 1914; Feb. 13, 1915; Mar. 15, 1915; July 14, 1917, 1920, 1922 undated; Feb. 14, 1923; Nov. 7, 1927
Hobbs, William Herbert, 1864-1953.
Jan. 31, 1911; Nov. 28, 1913; Sept. 10, 1914; Nov. 24, 1915; Dec. 24, 1915; Mar. 21, 1916; July 5, 1926
Holt, Hamilton, 1872-1951.
Nov. 18, 1918
Hubbard, Lucius Lee, 1849-1933
1911-1912; Aug. 26, 1913, 1914-1918; Feb. 8, 1919; Nov. 25, 1919, 1920; Apr. 1, 1921, 1922-1923; Sept. 21, 1924, 1925-1933
Hudson, Grant Martin, 1868-1955.
Feb. 7, 1907; Jan. 26, 1915; Apr. 1, 1915; May 26, 1924; Feb. 1909, 1911-1912; Mar. 23, 1916, 1917; May 3, 1920, 1925-1926, 1928-1933; May 25, 1934; Feb. 21, 1935, 1937; Jan. 8, 1938; Aug. 30, 1938
Sleeper, Albert E, 1862-1934.
Sept. 18, 1908; Dec. 23, 1915; Apr. 17, 1917; May 4, 1917
Smith, Henry Cassorte, 1859-1911.
Aug. 1, 1901; Sept. 27, 1901; Oct. 8, 1901
Smith, John, 1853-1923.
1907, 1910; Jan. 4, 1911; Aug. 9, 1911; Mar. 16, 1912; June 24, 1912; Jan. 7, 1915; Dec. 25, 1915, 1916; Oct. 12, 1917; Apr. 15, 1918; June 24, 1918; July 5, 1921; Mar. 5, 1923
Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.
Correspondence throughout
Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.
Dec. 18, 1905; Feb. 19, 1907, 1908; Apr. 25, 1910; Oct. 22, 1910; June 14, 1911; June 27, 1911; May 7, 1912; June 15, 1912, 1914; Mar. 25, 1915; Mar. 26, 1915; Feb. 12, 1916; Apr. 30, 1917; Dec. 9, 1917; Aug. 6, 1918
Spaulding, Thomas Marshall, 1882-
Undated; May 8, 1911; May 23, 1911; Mar. 5, 1923; Dec. 21, 1924; Apr. 10, 1925; Dec. 18, 1925; Feb. 11, 1926; Nov. 1, 1926, 1927-1928; Jan. 23, 1929; Feb. 6, 1930; Jan. 7, 1931; Jan. 9, 1932; Mar. 22, 1932
Stone, Ralph, 1868-1956.
1924-1937; Aug. 5, 1938; Jan. 28, 1939; Oct. 17, 1940
Taft, William Howard, 1857-1930.
Letters regarding his renomination in 1912; also regarding support for the Canadian Reciprocity Treaty; June 1911; December 30, 1911; March 1912; April 1912
Townsend, Charles E. (Charles Elroy), 1856-1924.
1904; Dec. 9, 1905, 1908; Jan. 12, 1909; Feb. 7, 1910; Dec. 31, 1910; July 24, 1911; May 7, 1912; May 9, 1912; July 8, 1913; Nov. 2, 1913; Dec. 26, 1914; Feb. 22, 1915, 1916; May 12, 1917, 1921-1922
Tyler, Moses Coit, 1835-1900
Jan. 22; 1898
U.S. Fuel Administration.
1918-1919
Vandenberg, Artbur Hendrick, 1862-1937.
Jan. 14, 1915; Jan. 19, 1915; Apr. 22, 1918; June 28, 1921; Apr. 6, 1928; June 4, 1928; Aug. 15, 1929; Apr. 22, 1932, 1933; Nov. 13, 1934; Mar. 22, 1935; Sept. 4, 1935; Feb. 17, 1937; July 8, 1938; July 26, 1938
Vaughan, Coleman C., 1857-
Aug. 19, 1902; Feb. 1, 1908; Feb. 15, 1908; Nov. 17, 1909; Sept. 19, 1910, 1914-1915; Apr. 11, 1916; Dec. 26, 1916, 1917; July 27, 1920; Feb. 18, 1924
Vaughan, Victor Clarence, 1851-1929.
Sept. 10, 1908; Dec. 1, 1908; Mar. 31, 1909; Sept. 25, 1909; Nov. 30, 1909; Apr. 11, 1910; Feb. 16, 1914; Oct. 26, 1914; Oct. 26, 1914; Sept. 7, 1915
Warner, Fred Maltby, 1865-1923.
Oct. 3, 1901; Nov. 15; 1904, 1905; 1908-1910; Jan. 11, 1915; Dec. 17, 1917, 1918, 1920, 1922
Washington, Booker Taliferro, 1858-1915.
Jan. 2, 1915; Oct. 14, 1915
Watkins, Lucius Whitney, 1873-
July 8, 1909; July 19, 1909; Aug. 7, 1910; Apr. 9.1912; Apr. 26, 1912; Feb. 6, 1915; Mar. 24, 1915; Apr. 4, 1923; Dec. 11, 1939
Wedemeyer, William Walter, 1873-1913.
1910-1912
Wenley, Robert Mark, 1861-1929.
Oct. 11, 1904; Feb. 2, 1909; Oct. 28, 1909; June 10, 1915; Nov. 15, 1917; Sept. 22, 1922; Jan. 11, 1926; Mar. 2, 1926; Jan. 11, 1927; Mar. 28, 1929
White, William Allen, 1868-1944.
May 28, 1929
Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924.
(Letters concerning support for Wilson as president of the University of Michigan); June 23, 1909; Aug. 2, 1909; August 13, 1909; November 11, 1909
Wood, Leonard, 1860-1927.
Jan. 16, 1922
Worcester, Dean Conant, 1866-1924.
Apr. 24, 1911; Nov. 15, 1912; Oct. 14, 1914
Yost, Fielding Harris, 1871-1946.
Feb. 3, 1917, 1921; May 16, 1922; Jan. 30, 1924; Mar. 17, 1925; Jan. 25, 1926; Oct. 3, 1927; June 19, 1928; June 25, 1929; Sept. 18, 1930; Jan. 8, 1931, 1935